♪ Fixed & Synced by bozxphd.Enjoy The Flick ♪
Is this the one we saw
in the ad the other day?
There you are.
You liked it and here it is.
Thank you. Thank you, dear.
You are a wonderful wife.
You mean I am the best.
Isn't that right?
- Let me serve the breakfast.
- Yes.
- I must leave now, love.
- Already?
- Bye.
- Bye, sweetheart.
- How about the outing, Papa?
- The outing? Tomorrow, dear.
- No, Papa. Today!
- You promised her for today.
- Papa please. Today.
- Have you forgotten?
- Papa please.
- I'm helpless love. I can't find the time.
- Today, Papa please.
- Tomorrow, I promise. No engagements.
- Shekhar you...
Leave immediately or
she'll kick up a fuss.
Papa please.
I'll take care of her. You are getting
late, isn't it? Go on - Please dear.
- Papa please. Today.
- Leave the tie. Bye.
All right now.. you could've at least
said a proper good-bye to Papa, darling.
You mustn't cry. Can Mama
take you for an outing then?
Stop crying. Where do you want to go?
- Wonder world?
- Yes.
Yes.
Is it fun?
Are you having fun?
Mother..
Mother.. papa is there.
Papa? Where?
Papa! Papa!
Papa!
Mama, call out to him.
Mother.
I've always told you, Shekhar.
We must tell Sarita everything about us.
How would that help?
I know Sarita very well.
She'll never accept you.
Hush dear.. quiet.
Now look Shekhar. Whatever Sarita
says to you, just keep quiet. Please.
Even if she asks you to separate
from me, just agree to it.
- Because she has the first right to you.
- You have as much right to me, Renu.
Neither can I separate from her, nor you.
- It's time Sarita faces the truth.
- You're wrong, Shekhar. You know...
Now look, she must give you
as much respect as you give her.
Shekhar.
You.. you...
You are terribly hurt, aren't you?
Which is why I didn't want to tell you?
Your daddy did a lot of favours to me.
I couldn't refuse to marry you.
I did my best to forget Renu.
But destiny brought us
together once again.
Forgive me, Sarita. Forgive me.
Forgive..
Sarita, there's another thing.
My Shalu has no one else
in the world.
Accept her, Sarita.
Who would be a better mother than you?
For my sake.
I beg of you, Sarita.
Give me a promise.
Give me your word, please.
Please Sarita, please.
"There is laughter, there are tears.
Life is all about joys and sorrows."
"There is autumn and there is Spring."
"Seasons come and go."
"There is laughter, there are tears.
Life is all about joys and sorrows."
"lf one sleeps, protected...
...another craves for compassion."
"lf one is distraught...
...another is showered with love."
"lf there is pain...
..there is a balm."
"Life is all about joys and sorrows."
"There is laughter, there are tears."
"Memories of days gone by...
...continue to torment us."
"Like shadows,
they come to haunt us."
"Like shadows, they go away."
"Loneliness casts a pall of gloom...
...for life is all about
joys and sorrows."
"There is autumn and there is Spring."
"Seasons come and go."
"One is forced to live...
...for there are social mores."
"There are days when
you gain and lose...
...days when there are
promises to keep."
"Restlessness overwhelms."
"Life is all about joys and sorrows."
I think this scarf is horrible.
- Hi, sis. You look great.
- I'm trying to.
Junior!
- Why're you so nervous?
- I told you.
Officers from the bank I applied for
a loan from are coming to see me today.
So what's there to be nervous about?
One look at you and they'll
give you the whole bank...
...and say, You may repay the
money whenever you wish to.
And don't repay it,
if you don't want to.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Good morning, Mother.
- Good morning dear.
Good morning, Mother.
- How often have I told you Shalu...?
- That I mustn't slide like this.
- Yes.
- I can't help it, Mama. I always forget.
Sorry.
- I am nervous, Mother.
- You just don't worry, Nimmi.
- Just talk to them with confidence.
- Not confidence, Ma. Over-confidence.
Over-confidence is the trend nowadays.
Don't joke about everything, Shalu.
Not everything in life is a joke.
- But...
- I wonder why she talks nonsense.
All right, I'll leave.
- All the best.
- Shalu.
Junior.
Oh, God.
See what junior has done!
- I wonder why you like dogs so much.
- Mother..
Because you don't like them.
In any case, is there anything about me
that you approve of? What do you like?
Whatever I say is wrong,
whatever I think is wrong.
Whatever I wear is wrong.
And I think it's wrong for me
to even stay here.
- Shalu.
- Nimmi.
- See? She does it deliberately!
- Let her be, Mama.
Hi.
Rangeela, looks like she's had
a problem with her mother again.
Shalu.. did you have another
argument with your mother?
What is the matter, Shalu?
- Want to see her happy?
- Oh yes!
In that case, tell her right away
that you're in love with her!
Sure.. no, what if it
spoils her mood even more?
Keep getting scared and you'll keep
me company all your life! Tell her!
- No, I can't tell her.
- Either you tell her, or I will!
- Shalu...
- Shut up. One moment. I'll tell her.
Shalu, there's something
I want to tell you.
- Shalu, I...
- What?
- Actually, I...
- Go on, Sameer.
Well, I have a special show!
I want you to attend it.
- You will, won't you?
- You're an ass!
Okay, I'll surely come.
Bye.
Ladies and Gentlemen.
Forgive me for calling you over
for a meeting at such short notice.
But this is an emergency.
Khanna Industries has paid the farmers
of apples such a low price, this year...
...that the farmers have started
an agitation against them.
I tried to telephone Mr. Khanna.
But despite the best of my efforts...
Efforts! Efforts is what you have
been doing for the last fifteen days.
When will your efforts end?
When the apples have rotted?
When people are already starving?
Why ask her? She's of no use!
What are we to tell the farmers
in our village?
- What do you mean?
- They're rich folks.
How would they understand
the sufferings of the poor?
There's no point in talking to them.
It's of no use!
Please try to understand
the point I'm making.
I know Mr. Khanna very well.
What's the matter, Principal?
What's the fuss all about?
How do I explain, dear?
Mittal and his men are taking
advantage of the situation...
...to dislodge Sarita-ji
from the Mayor's chair.
I assure you, should you choose me
as the mayor...
- ...I'll see your troubles vanish.
- I'll make you the Mayor, Mr. Mittal!
What are you doing? That much of chilli
will set their tongues on fire!
Is that all?
- And now?
- It'll come out of their ears!
Sarita-ji, whatever happens,
I'll raise my voice for my people.
I'll see that they have their right,
because I don't wear bangles like you.
Wow. Wonderful. Great.
Fantastic, Uncle Mittal! After that
fiery line, you must surely take a break.
Coming up, yogurt-fries,
made specially by me.
- Try some.
- No.
Sit down, Uncle Mittal.
Here you are.
Urvashi, serve it to everyone.
- Please have it.
- Thank you.
Had I been the Mayor,
I'd immediately solve...
Tasty, isn't it?
What happened?
It's excellent, dear!
Thank you, Uncle.
One won't do, here's another.
You, too.
You have it as well. I've made it.
This is only the beginning,
Uncle Mayor. Have more.
Chilli!
What happened?
Try some more. What happened?
Chilli.
What is the matter, Uncle Mittal?
Have another.
Have it.
Come.. come.
Look at what your daughter has done!
Look at her misbehaviour!
- What's all this?
- No need to pretend, lady.
- You're the one who did all this!
- Watch your tongue, Mittal!
- Quiet!
- But he's a cheapskate, Mama!
He wants to instigate people against
you and himself become the Mayor.
Fantastic, Sarita-ji! Nice way of
humiliating me through your daughter!
Let's go! There's no meeting
take place here!
- Yes.
- Let's go, everyone.
Go away. Get lost.
- Please hear me out.
- You'll have to pay for this, Sarita-ji.
- You surely will! Let's go, everyone!
- Go away. Get lost!
Mr. Mittal please listen to me.
Whatever happens, you can
never be the Mayor!
- Shalu, what insolence is this?
- This was the only way...
- ...of straightening out Mittal, Mama.
- It's your way, maybe.
With what you've done, you've left
no stone unturned in humiliating me!
- But it was only for...
- Shalu, you are good for nothing. Okay.
You will do nothing for yourself,
and interfere in my affairs.
You will be able to achieve
nothing in life! Go away.
Get lost, I say.
Mother.
Shalu.
Are you very angry?
Even with me?
Shalu.
You mustn't cry.
Sit down.
It's okay if Mama scolds me.
But why does she say
such nasty things to me?
- Am I her enemy?
- No, Shalu. That's not how it is.
- You're mistaken.
- Am I really? I'll show you.
Look. How lovingly Mama holds you
and she doesn't even touch me.
Look at this, it's the
same story even in this one.
Look at this. This!
And this is what I have
endured since my childhood!
Don't be stupid, Shalu.
You're only imagining the worst.
It's nothing else.
Sis, the one who has to endure it,
will know how it feels.
You have always got love from Mama.
But I...?
I feel as if I were picked from a fair.
What nonsense!
Mama loves you as much as she loves me.
I can't hear such things against Mama.
Then don't talk to me.
Because that's just what
I'm going to tell you.
- Yes, I won't talk to you.
- Then get out my room.
- This is not only your room.
- Of course, it is.
- No, it isn't.
- Don't ask me for any money!
- I won't! Mama's side-kick.
- Don't vent your anger on me.
- Mama's side-kick!
- Stop it, Shalu. Don't ask me...
- Mother's side-kick.
Rangeela, she hasn't turned up yet.
She's not coming!
Sit on your thumb!
One mustn't stay
where one is not respected.
I'm leaving!
What a predicament! I don't even
have the money to leave home!
God! Have mercy on Shalu.
I don't want alms.
- So where are you all set to go?
- Sameer has a show, he has invited me.
Have you asked Mama?
My darling sister,
that's your department.
Take care of Mama. I'll think it over.
Please, I'm getting late. Here I go!
- Okay, bye.
- Have fun.
- I am sorry.
- It's okay.
"Even if you say nothing...
...my love."
"Your eyes do convey...
...your love for me."
"Even if you say nothing...
...my love.
"Your eyes do convey...
...your love for me."
"Why are there beads of perspiration..."
"...on your forehead?"
"Do not lower your gaze...
...when you see me."
"I know, you do pine for me...
...deep down in your heart."
"Your eyes do convey...
...your love for me."
"Face to face with you...
...I felt shy."
"I was tongue-tied...
...such was the effect on me."
"Every moment..."
"...I wait for you."
"Your eyes do convey...
...your love for me."
Wow!
Wow. Sameer, you are great, excellent,
mind-blowing and amazing.
Congratulations, Mr. Sameer.
- Thank you.
- These folks from Japan...
...think you're a great artist.
- Hello. Thank you.
- They want to take you along to Japan.
- Hello.
- What?
- You must come. You must come.
- Wow.
No, I'm not going.
What's happening?
He is refusing to come to Japan.
Sameer, at least think about me.
When you go to Japan and make a name
for yourself, won't it make me happy?
Don't you want me to tell the whole
world that you are my Sameer?
So that's how it is!
Here we go then to Japan!
Yes, he's coming to Japan.
- He's coming to Japan.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you Mr. Sameer.
- Good bye.
- Thank you very much.
- Hello. I am Shalu.
- Wow.
This is great. You do look nice in
those clothes you pinched from me.
- Got any money on you?
- Yes, I do.
But may I ask,
where is the royal entourage headed?
- On work.
- What?
Come again.
Why not? Can only Mama and you work?
- What? Are you serious, Shalu?
- Yes, Sister.
Oh Shalu, I am so happy for you.
I am so happy.
I want to prove it to Mama
that I can achieve something too.
- That's okay. But where are you going?
- Khanna Industries.
Wow. Khanna. Khanna Industries?
But they're in the red
and they're sacking people.
Obviously, because
I haven't been there yet.
See what happens when I get there.
Khanna Industries is going to thrive.
- They will run in profit again.
- Okay.
- How will you find a job there?
- No place on earth, sis...
- ...where Shalu won't find a job!
- Shalu.
Yes, Mama?
Wish you all the best.
Thank you, Mother.
- Mr. Roopchand?
- Shame! Shame!
- Mr. Roopchand Khoobchand?
- Khanna Industries.
- Shame! Shame.
Fulfill our demands.
- Excuse me! Excuse me!
- Fulfill our demands.
Mr. Roopchand Khoobchand?
Shame! Shame.
- Hello.
- Someone's here to see you.
- Who?
- Shalu.
- Shalu?
- Yes.
Wait.
Junior, it's some Shalu.
She says she has an appointment.
Only the Food Inspector
was supposed to come today.
- The new Food Inspector? We've had it!
- Yes.
We have trouble out there and
here's the Food Inspector.
Call her in! Call her in!
- Hello.
- Yes, sir.
- Send Shalu in.
- Okay sir.
- Junior, show me the stock-statement.
- At least comb your hair!
- What comb?
- Your wig!
Good morning...
Wow! Great hair!
- Straighten it.
- Why're you doing that?
- It looked nice the way it was.
- It was turned around.
That was a different style,
absolutely novel.
- Was it?
- Believe me.
- Yes!
- How about my hair?
- Yours is nice too.
- Oh, yes.
- But they won't turn around like his.
- They sure do look!
Mind blowing.
- You like our hair so much?
- Oh yes.
- They're real!
- When did I say they're fake?
Please sit down.
What can we do for you?
Don't ask. Just send for
something hot or cold.
Hold it. Sweetie, send some
tea and fries.
- Madam, it was nice talking to you.
- Me too.
- You and we are going to work together!
- Absolutely. That's what I want too.
- Just tell me what my job will be.
- The Food Inspector before you...
...Mr. Badhudhi, he came inspecting us
only once every month.
- With his eyes, ears and mouth shut!
- Just don't worry.
I'll write a better report than he did.
With my eyes, ears and mouth..
Everything shut.
- That's nice of you!
- Child's play for me.
Just tell me how much money
you will pay me.
You do talk about everything openly!
- Wow!
- Must say, women are fast nowadays.
- We have a budget of 10,000 Rupees.
- 10,000?
Every month. We'll pay in advance.
And in cash.
Here's 10,000 Rupees. Count it.
Thank you.
There's no need to count it,
but I will.
- Sure. Go ahead!
Congratulations.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven.
What? The Food Inspector can't come?
But she's already here, you moron!
A man? One moment!
You aren't a man, are you?
No!
There's a misunderstanding.
I'll find out and call back.
- Who are you?
- Shalu.
- I'm Roopchand! Glad to meet you.
- Me, too.
- My brother, Khoobchand.
- Aren't you the Food Inspector?
- When did I say that?
- Set it right!
- Is mine okay?
- One moment. Mine?
Yes, it's okay.
Cheat! Fraud!
- What are you here for?
- Tell us quickly.
- For the job.
- Job?
- How dare you come in here?
- For a job!
I want to pull your company
out of the red and...
- You get out first! Get out!
- What are you doing?
- Get out!
- You're making a mistake.
- You're going to regret it.
- Get out.
Listen to that.
- Junior let's go.
- Yes brother.
- Roopchand.
- Shame! Shame!
- Khoobchand.
Fulfill our demands.
- Fulfill our demands.
- Calm down. Calm down!
Beat them up! Beat them up!
Listen to me.
Stop it! Calm down.
We're with you! We want your
welfare. Junior you tell them.
Believe us and go home.
We'll do what we can.
All right, we'll go away.
But we won't spare you...
...if you don't settle our demands
by tomorrow! Let's go!
- Wasn't he acting tough?
- He'll quit doing that.
- Who does he think he is?
- Brother.
- Such a nuisance.
- Brother so what happens tomorrow?
What else?
They have just two ways, Junior.
Either let the apples rot or sell
at half the price and make money.
- Mittal sure had a brainwave, brother.
- True.
It's only a matter of time, Junior.
The day Khanna Industries is sold.
Mittal will buy it and make us his
equal partners, as he promised to.
What a great day that will be!
What's she doing here?
- She was listening to our conversation.
- What if she tells someone?
- Let me ask. Wait.
- Ask her.
- Hey Shalu, what are you doing here?
- Well, I...
You haven't heard something, have you?
- I've heard.
- What?
We aren't going to be afraid.
What did you hear?
- Everything.
- What? Everything?
- Yes. Everything.
- Now look, don't tell anyone.
Not even Khanna Uncle?
- You know Khanna?
- Sure.
I've played with him
since I was a child.
- Played with him?
- Played with him?!
Yes.
He telephones me every day and
treats me like his own daughter.
So why didn't you tell us?
Send for the tea.
Sit down, dear. Sit down
I don't want a job I get
out of a recommendation.
What recommendation? You've been
like a child to our master.
Mr. Khanna is our boss. Brother,
that job of assistant manager.
- Give it to her.
- A salary of 5,000 rupees.
Rs. 5000?
- Only Rs. 5000? No.
- Rs. 7000. Is that enough?
Rs. 7000 is all right, but there are
no guarantees on leaking information.
- All right then. Rs. 10,000 is final.
- Do we have the guarantee now?
100 percent guarantee.
You won't complain against us
to Mr. Khanna, will you?
What complaint? Which Mr. Khanna?
- Mr. Khanna.
- Dad.
Dad.
Dev, my son. How was your day?
Terrible day, dad. I've never seen
so much of mismanagement in my life.
It is so... disorganized.
- Which factory of mine is like that?
- Which one? All of them are!
You've surely been to
someone else's factory.
As far as I know,
not only my managers...
...even my clerks are educated guys.
- They all are qualified.
- Qualified.
- Yes.
- Dad.
None of your managers has any idea
of Chang's Theory of Productivity.
Neither do they know about Dang's
Theory of Non-productivity.
Nor do they know about Fang's Theory
of Productivity of Non-productivity.
Now what's all that about?
That's the problem, dad.
You know nothing
about the theories either.
- Sad.
- Very sad.
Very, very sad.
Oh, yes, dad.
With these CEO's, I have decided
to shut down our plant in Palampur.
What for?
For the last five years, it has been
incurring heavy losses, dad.
- Right.
My son, one must not worry
only about his own profits.
One must do things even for
the welfare of the others.
Oh, dad. Dad.
Why do you get so emotional, dad?
Chang's golden rule.
There are no sentiments in business.
My son, it's because of our factory
that people in that city make a living.
Okay dad, here's what we'll do.
I'll go there personally and find out
why the factory is incurring losses.
It's okay if we can find a cure.
Else, the factory is closed.
- What?
- Okay.
Come on dad. I am being fare enough.
- Okay. When do you want to leave?
- I'll go today itself.
I am so happy.
Dev, will you go there
just like that?
- What do you mean?
- I mean...
...lf you go there as Dev, the truth
behind the problems will never emerge.
Yes, Chang's theory of
business in disguise.
Business in disguise.
Dad, I'll go there not as your son Dev,
but as Anand, your chauffeur's son.
Just give me an appointment letter
for the job of a clerk.
What's one letter?
I'll give you ten, my son.
Just get there quickly
and take up the job tomorrow.
- Great dad. Murthy.
- Sir.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Come on.
- Mission Palampur.
- Yeah.
Wait, wait. Where's Khanna Industries?
Hey! Where's Khanna Industries?
Shit. Shit.
Where have I landed?
Hey.
- Me?
- Yes, you. Come here.
Where.. where the hell is this.. I mean...
...I mean where's Khanna Industries?
Where's Khanna Industries? Khanna. Khanna.
- Kanha.. Kanha.. Kanha.
- Yes. Yes.
What?
What are you saying?
Can't you speak Hindi?
Oh god! Hindi, Gujarati, French, Italian,
you surely know some language?
Hey.. hey.. go away.
Keep them away.. away!
Go away. Go away.
- What's up, mister? You're fuming.
- Where is Khanna Industries?
- So you want to go to Khanna Industries?
- I wish to go Delhi!
I said Khanna Industries only to
start a conversation with you.
This is where you'll get a bus
for Delhi, at 8 tonight.
Hey! Hey!
You...
Hey!
Yes.
Do you know where
Khanna Industries is?
- Very bad. They shouldn't have done that.
- Who?
- The bus-conductor.
- Why?
They have a battle going with
the government nowadays...
...for a salary hike. But to vent their
anger on the passengers, is not done.
They must fight the government.
Isn't it?
- All right, but what is the matter?
- What else?
There was this passenger here yesterday
who said he wanted to see the Qutub Minar.
- But the Qutub Minar is in Delhi.
- I know that too.
But that's what they told him
when he got off. That this is Delhi.
Delhi?
- And Delhi's 300 kilometers away.
- 300 kilometers? I've had it!
You won't have to travel that far.
You wish to go to
Khanna Industries, right?
- It's four kilometers away.
- Four kilometers?
- Yes. See that hill?
- That one?
- Yes, that tall one.
- Behind that?
Oh no. Climb down that hill and
you will come across a small lake.
- Lake.
- And then..
"Take my beloved across
the river, O boatman."
- What was that?
- The song the boatman sings.
- Boatman song?
- Yes. And listen...
...don't ask anyone for
the address around here.
They're experts at making
fools out of people.
No, I won't ask them.
I'm not a fool, am I?
- Of course.
- Khanna Industries.
You shouldn't have done that
to the poor guy, Shalu.
No poor guy. That's just what
the arrogant man deserved.
We're having our laughs here
and he must be climbing the hill.
Yes, what he doesn't know...
...is that although there is
a way to climb the hill...
Oh, I am safe.
But there is no way for him to climb down.
Oh, my God.
I am dead.
Take my beloved across
the river, O boatman.
"Take my beloved across
the river, O boatman."
Here you are, mister.
Khanna Industries.
- Here you are fifty rupees.
- All right, go on.
This is the point from where I set
out the day before yesterday!
Khanna Industries is right there.
So that girl was...
If I find her again.
I'll pluck her hair out!
I'll strangle her!
I'm not sparing her!
- Give us an answer.
- What sort of a question is that?
If you wish to interview me, ask me
something to do with my work.
We're the ones interviewing you.
So we'll ask whatever we wish to!
- So what do you think of our hair?
- Your hair?
Yes.
Third-rate! Obviously,
you guys are wearing wigs.
In those clothes,
you guys look like clowns in a circus.
And you guys talk like
illiterate village bumpkins.
What illiterate? I'm a graduate!
Watch your manners!
- What if I failed my grades in school?
- Never mind. He fails the interview!
- You're not getting the job. Get out!
- All right, now tell me something.
If the company's balance-sheets
aren't all right...
- ...which account does one look up?
- He's looking for a fight.
Who mooted the Theory of
Productivity of Non-productivity?
- You, brother?
- Not me.
Not us.
Are you interviewing us
or are we interviewing you?
When the two of you have no inkling
of these two basic theories...
...you have no right
to conduct interviews.
Who hired you, in any case?
I'll talk to dad today...
I mean, Mr. Khanna, right today,
and have you sacked.
Don't give us those threats.
Not threats. He's upset because
he has failed in the interview.
He has brought a letter from Mr. Khanna.
We'll have to consider that.
We've got to respect Mr. Khanna
after all.
Junior.
- Must we employ him?
- We must.
You are hired. Go on.
- You're large-hearted, brother.
- Never mind.
- Touch his feet. Hurry up!
- Never mind. Sit down.
Sir, we've got to deliver the goods
and there is no driver at all.
It'll be managed. This is Anand. He'll
keep records and also be the driver.
A clerk who will also
double as a driver?
Don't worry Mr. Roopchand.
I'll explain everything to him.
What name, did you say?
This is Ms. Shalu. You
have to work with her.
Dev Anand?
No, just Anand.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
I'll explain everything to him.
You don't worry, sir. Bye.
- You?
- I'll tell him that I'm his boss.
- Now look, Mister.
- Damn it! You rotten...
Do not get personal with me
Call me madam. I'm your boss.
To hell with the bosses!
4 kilometers to Khanna Industries?
The hill and the lake
and the boatman?
What are you talking about?
I hope you're all right?
You're the one who's going to be ill!
You're surely mistaken!
It must've been another girl.
- I've never seen you before.
- You won't again! I'm killing you!
- I'll report you to the bosses.
- Those baldies can't do anything to me.
Open the door!
I'm going to knock your teeth out!
First break the door,
you dumb idiot!
Really? Here goes!
"Take my beloved across
the river, O boatman."
- Stop! Stop!
- Narayan!
- What are you doing?
- And what are you doing here?
Never mind me.
What's gotten into you?
- You're going to ruin my plans.
- One moment.
Where were you for two days? Hello!
Your dad was so worried.
- So I came looking for you.
- How do I tell you...
...that girl made such a fool out of me!
I spent a night and a day in the jungle!
- A night with that girl? How romantic!
- With that girl? Never!
Sister he's a mere driver but
he behaves as if he's the employer.
You'll know when he beats you up.
Beat me up? Big deal.
- I must hang up now.
- What for?
There are tourists arriving in buses.
I've got to attend to them.
Want me to come and help you?
I'm absolutely free.
- Will they let you go?
- Why not?
Has anyone ever been able
to stop me?
Come over then. I'm hanging up.
- Okay, bye.
Excuse me, sir. This...
- Wow sir! Your hair is glistening!
- Really?
- Which shampoo do you use?
- We can't use any shampoo at all.
He means, our hair does not
need any shampoo at all.
- Right!
- That's amazing, sir.
- I wish I had hair like that too.
- Sure you will.. no?
- I want leave, sir.
- Leave?
- Sure. Go ahead.
- All right, go on.
And sir, I need a driver too.
Please.
Take that new driver.
He'll even be put to a test.
Yes, yes.
You mean Dev Anand?
He's so snooty.
If he is snooty then
even we are no less.
Just tell us if he bothers you.
We'll fix him. You've been treated
like a child by our master, after all.
Ever since I was a child.
Okay, sir, thank you. Bye.
- This girl's a bit too fast.
- Sure, she is.
I've got all the information
on the factory's condition.
The quality of production is terrible.
People are returning our goods.
The factory is in a very pathetic state.
- Very, very sad.
I don't know how we're going
to run this factory.
Remember Chang's fundamental rule?
When business gets out of control,
just shut it down.
Correct.
Narayan, let's prepare a report
after a complete investigation.
We're shutting down this factory.
- Perfect.
- Hey, driver.
- Here she is.
- Who?
- The manipulative one.
- She's quite a babe!
Hey, shut up.
Hey driver..
..get the car out.
Madam's got to go out.
What's all this?
Behave yourself okay.
I'm your boss. Should I complain
to those baldies...
...you'll lose your job in a second.
Sorry, madam.
Please go ahead. I'll follow you.
Stupid driver.
I think she's hand-in-glove
with those baldies!
Meaning? She uses a wig too?
Wig or no wig.
If I could get the opportunity
to straighten her out!
- So madam.
- Have you gone mad?
That man. Driver stupid.
You took me for a ride, didn't you?
Let me take you around Palampur now!
What are you doing driver?
Drive slowly!
Driver stupid stop!
Okay, okay. What happened?
Have you gone mad?
Is that how you drive?
- Don't you like the way I drive?
- I'll have you sacked!
Stupid driver.
Now look, Madam, don't keep
giving me those empty threats.
- I'm the son of Mr. Khanna's chauffeur.
- So what?
I know Khanna Uncle very well too.
If I report you to him...
- ...he'll sack you and your father!
- Since when is Mr. Khanna your uncle?
Since I was a child.
I've played with him.
- He loves me so much.
- What a liar?
- What did you say?
- Nothing. Shall we go?
Stupid driver. Drive slowly! Idiot.
- May I have it packed then?
- Yes.
Okay.
Driver, are you a tourist
on a holiday?
Go and have this packed.
Over there.
- Yes, madam.
- Carefully.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- Pack that chair too.
- Chair?
Yes.
Yes, madam.
I am so sorry.
Are you all right?
You're not hurt, are you?
- Answer me!
- Oh, sorry. I am fine.
Oh, my God. Thanks.
I thought I'd open my eyes only
in hospital. But you saved me.
Oh no, it was actually my mistake.
I was packing the chair, I didn't see
you taking things down from there so...
So here you are chatting away!
Didn't I ask you to pack the stuff?
- The customers are waiting.
- He saved me from falling down.
Hi, I am Nimmi.
Shalu's sister.
- I am Dev.
- Dev.
I mean Anand.
- He's the driver I told you about.
- Look, Madam. I'm no driver.
- I'm a graduate and a clerk.
- But you talk as if you are the boss.
So he's the bossy one?
- Has he thrashed you yet?
- Do you think he can thrash me?
Why're you listening to our chat?
Get on with your work.
- Yes, madam.
- Okay.
Hello, Narayan.
- I'm listening. Go on.
- How's your investigation going?
What will I tell you, Dev?
Everything is in a bad shape.
- I'll have to go into the details.
- Quickly do whatever you've got to.
That girl has made life
miserable for me.
Hang on. I'll do it. Come on.
- What are you showing me?
- Look at this.
- This.
- This is bad.
- Look.
- Very bad.
- Look at this sir.
- Very, very, very bad.
- Why's the C.A. here?
- Dev has sent him here.
He has checked all the books
and says things are so bad...
- ...we'll have to shut down the factory.
- That's just what we want, Roopchand.
What for?
If the factory does not close down,
how are we going to buy it?
You're right, but if the factory
closes down...
...the farmers will kick up a racket.
Their yield of apples will rot.
Let their yield rot.
It's time to harvest our crop now.
I'll show you at the Town Hall today,
what happens when you kick a hungry man.
Long live the Farmers' Union.
Meet our demands.
- Long live the Farmers' Union.
- Please come, come inside.
Meet our demands.
At least hear me out.
I assure you, we'll surely find
a solution to this problem.
How is it possible?
We know none of the problem
is going to be solved, Sarita-ji.
Remember, when we had a crisis
last year, I spoke to Mr. Khanna...
...and got him to pay us 700 Rupees
for every quintal of apples.
- And I...
- Well, well!
We are not here to discuss
what happened last year.
We want to know what's
happening this year.
I have a request to make to
the members of the Committee.
Give me just 24 hours to convince
Mr. Khanna to think in your favour.
You're right, Sarita-ji.
I agree with her.
- We must give Sarita-ji the 24 hours.
- Sure, we must.
- Say it! We must.
- Yes, we must.
- We must.
All right!
We give her another 24 hours.
They have a lot of hopes
pinned on you, you see.
But we will meet here again
tomorrow to see...
...how you shatter their hopes.
Principal, I've decided to personally
go to Delhi and talk to Mr. Khanna.
- Delhi? Now? At this hour?
- Yes principal sir.
We have very little time.
If Mittal becomes the Mayor...
...we know what's going to
happen to the farmers.
- Of course.
- I'll do my best to save...
...this city from disaster.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Sarita-ji, what happened?
- Madam.. Madam.. Madam.
- Ms. Sarita, what happened?
Madam.. Madam.. Madam.
- What happened to Mama, doctor?
- Nothing to worry about.
Your mother suffers from hyper-tension.
I've given her a tranquilizer...
...she only needs to rest.
Dev is the root cause of all
the problems! He's a devil!
He wants to shut down the factory!
Who does he think he is?
- I'm not going to spare him!
- Nor am I.
- We must do something for Mama, sis.
- That's just what I can't figure out.
Think of something, Shalu!
- Sis! I have a mind-blowing idea!
- I know what you're thinking about.
- Lf Mama can't go to Delhi then...
- The two of us can.
Yes.
But one of us ought
to stay with Mama.
I'll be the one to go, darling.
I'll give Mr. Khanna such sound logic...
- ...that he'll have to agree.
- Sis dear...
...logic isn't what
always works in life.
It's time to do something drastic
and make Khanna toe our line.
Till Khanna and that bloody Dev
don't agree...
...I'm not budging from there.
Good.
All right, but whom will you
go with at this hour of the night?
Leave that to me. Let me see
what stuff this Dev is made of.
He has ruined our sleep.
An apple? Who's hurling apples at me?
Who is it?
You?
Hey driver, come down here.
- But I...
- Come down, I say.
Madam.
- Madam, where are we going?
- Just drive along this road.
And don't disturb me, okay?
- This road goes to Delhi.
- Really? We're going to Delhi too.
- What for?
- To meet Mr. Khanna or his son.
What? To meet Dev? Are you mad?
Why do you stop the car
without a reason?
Is it a disease? At this rate,
we won't make it to Delhi in 6 months.
Sure and what are you going
to achieve in Delhi anyway?
Take my advice. Let's return.
Mr. Dev is not changing his decision.
Really?
In that case, I'll give your Dev sir
such a kung-fu punch...
...he'll be exorcised
of the American smartness.
What you punch me?
I mean you'll give Dev a punch?
What are you worth?
A driver talking about worth!
You'll know my worth when
I give your Dev a nice kick.
Oh really? Dev's enemy is my enemy.
And I don't drive for the enemy.
Drive to Delhi on your own.
Oh sure, I will.
Do you think I can't drive a car?
What's the big deal anyway? Just start
the car, change the accelerator...
- ...step on the brakes.
- You'll know.
Look, driver!
Don't ever challenge me, okay?
Help. Help.
Why's this car going backwards?
Driver.
Driver. Stop this car.
Delhi's on this side, Madam.
Not over there!
I know! And I wish I could
drive the car over Dev!
Oh my god! Where's the car going?
Madam, the brakes.
What brake? Where is it?
- Why don't you say anything?
- Madam, the brakes.
Stupid driver, tell me where they are.
Oh my god!
Madam.
Madam.. Madam.. Madam.
- Are you okay, madam?
- Fix the car first!
I'll deal with you later.
- How much more time will it take?
- About 10 minutes.
- Hurry up!
- Sure, that's what I'm doing.
Wow! She's so beautiful.
"What intoxication is this?"
"It appears as if I'm falling in love."
"Pining is so much of fun, too."
"In her eyes, she has hidden me away."
"There's this lovely face
that has robbed me of my peace."
"There's love in the air."
"The gentle breeze
blows my scarf away."
"The one in my heart is my beloved."
"It appears as if I'm falling in love."
"Pining is so much of fun, too."
"I'm beginning to go crazy about you."
"I'm being consumed by thoughts
hitherto alien to me."
"I didn't even get to realise it."
"When my desire for you awakened?"
"There's a pain, there's an ache,
and there's a feeling of shyness."
"I feel as if I'm falling in love."
"What intoxication is this?"
"Pining is so much of fun."
"I feel as if I'm falling in love."
"I feel as if."
"I feel as if..."
"...I'm falling in love."
Dev stop.
- I'm falling in love.
- Stupid driver.
I'm falling...
Stupid driver.
- Driver! Hurry up!
- Coming, ma'am.
Quite a dangerous girl, I say.
There are no sentiments in business.
Chang is always right.
Hello! Murthy? It's Dev, you idiot.
Now listen, there's this girl
coming with me to meet Papa.
She mustn't get to meet him,
come what may.
Because I'm sure Papa will
fall into her trap.
I'm hanging up now.
Coming madam.
Dev.
- Everything's taken care of!
- Okay, do something about the girl.
Don't worry. I'll handle her.
Excuse me, madam.
I am Murthy. Can I help you?
I'm Shalu.
I'm here to meet either Mr. Khanna
or his son, Dev.
And it is very urgent.
Mr. Khanna is asleep.
And Dev isn't at home right now.
- He's gone out for a party.
- Oh, no.
Please wake him up. Please.
Please wake him up!
I'm sorry, I can't even disturb him.
Please leave.
- Leave? What do you mean?
- Madam.
I haven't travelled 300 kilometers
to be asked to leave!
Calm down! Please don't
make a noise, Madam!
- No noise, you'll wake him up.
- That's just what I want!
I'll do what I want to.
I'll shout and scream.
- Mr. Khanna. Help!
- Pick her up.
- Stop it. Stop it.
- Help!
- Who's that girl?
- She's asking for a donation sir.
- Throw her out!
- I don't want any donation.
- Get out. Driver, throw her out.
- Excuse me, wait a minute.
- Please wait.
- Get out. Where is she? Got her. Sorry..
Mr. Khanna, please try to understand.
The people of Palampur...
...are eagerly waiting for you or
Mr. Dev Khanna to do something for them.
You have always helped them, sir
But will you desert them now?
- Listen, my child...
- Don't let her mislead you, Dad!
- The poor girl is right.
- Uncle.
There are no sentiments in business, dad.
I'm sorry, my dear. But Dev will
now do whatever needs to be done.
Madam, we have sympathies for you.
But as we told you...
...this is Mr. Dev's decision and
we can't do anything about it.
In that case, I'll wait
for your Mr. Dev...
...and not leave till that
idiot has changed his mind!
There is the possibility of Dev
not returning all night, Madam.
- Right.
- I will wait for him forever!
Okay, please.
You may wait for him as you like.
But here's wishing you a good night.
I'm going to bed, too.
Wake me up, when you want to leave.
Till then, bye.
Madam, bye.
Listen child...
- ...I have an idea.
- What idea?
- That driver of yours.
- That moron?
Whatever he is,
I think he looks a lot like Dev.
Infact, they resemble each other so
much, even we are deceived at times.
- What are you trying to tell me?
- Suppose Dev does not turn up...
- ...we could...
- We could?
- ...we could perhaps.
- Perhaps...?
One moment!
Are you asking me to take that moron
back with me to Palampur as Dev?
Oh yes!
What's wrong in doing that
for a couple of hours?
As soon as Dev returns,
I'll have a word with him...
...and bring him to Palampur too.
Everything will fall in place.
- Really?
- Yes.
Oh, yes. Thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I'm now going to fix that driver.
So this is where the moron is sleeping.
How dare he sleep in his master's bed?
Silly driver.
Hey, get up!
Lazybones! Wake up!
Madam, ever since you've come
into my life, I've lost my sleep.
That's all right. Get ready quickly,
we've got to leave.
And wear this. Go on.
Okay, madam.
My car-keys.
It'll take you there faster.
Thank you, Uncle.
Is it okay if I call you uncle?
Why not?
Why're you doing all this for me?
I like your spirit.
And perhaps you're the only one
who can straighten out my crazy son.
Your driver will arrive any moment.
I must leave.
One moment.
You have my blessings.
Wow.
- You're a handsome guy.
- Really?
- Happy now, Madam?
- Of course.
Nobody will get to know
that you're not Dev.
- There's something missing however.
- What?
There's something Dev sports
on his face. I must, too.
- What's this?
- Hold it.
- Boot-polish?
- Dev applies it on his face.
What are you doing?
Have you gone mad?
Hold on. How do I look now?
Handsome? Gorgeous?
I'm not going with you as Dev
at any cost!
Stupid driver.
Have you gone nuts?
Come here, open the door!
Stupid, idiot, driver. Open the door.
Do you folks see that?
Does that open your eyes at last?
Mr. Khanna is coming.
His son Dev is coming.
Has anyone turned up? No, sir!
What more is she going to do
to occupy that chair?
If you have any self-respect
or an iota of decency...
...accept defeat and tender
your resignation!
Yes, give resignation!
Mother. Mother.
Ma, Shalu is here!
There's someone else with her.
They are here.
- Where are the two of them?
- In that room, Madam.
Thank you.
- Shalu! Open the door! Quick!
- Coming, sis!
Please Anand! Why don't you agree?
- This is a very serious matter.
- Now listen, you chit of a girl!
I brought you here only
at Mr. Khanna's orders.
I'll never be a part of this farce.
A farce? The city's about to be
devastated, and you call it a farce?
It's all the results of the
wrong decisions Dev has taken.
Wrong decisions? Dev?
He has studied in America. He has
a first-class first degree!
What good is a degree that severs his
relationship with other human beings?
If this factory closes down,
many families will go to seed.
People will be forced
to sell their land.
In just a moment, the whole
of this city will be destroyed.
Come here, Anand.
Look at that small child.
Will anyone be able to
return his smile to him?
And that old farmer...
...he wonders what will happen of him,
if he's compelled to sell his land.
Where will he go? How will he
start life afresh, at this age?
Can't you feel their pain
and their suffering?
Can't you see the tears
they suppress in their eyes?
If I ever get to meet Dev and
come face to face with him...
...there's one question,
I'll surely ask him...
...what good is his study in America
or his degrees and theories...
...if he can't give these troubled
people any hope in life?
Anand, every man standing downstairs,
every woman and every farmer...
...wait in the hope that Dev will bring
a ray of hope for them...
- ...and fill their lives with joy.
- I'll fill their lives with joy.
I will.
I promise to play Dev for you.
- Really, Anand?
- Yes, Shalu.
Should you even ask me to pluck
the stars from the skies today...
...I'll do that for you.
I always misunderstood you.
But whatever you are.. you're wonderful.
Thank you, Anand. Thank you so much.
Sarita, why the suspense?
Where is Dev Khanna?
Mr. Mittal.. Mr. Mittal, here I am.
Hi, everybody.
Hi.
- Hi, Nimmi.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Have you gone mad, Shalu?
This poor chap is Anand!
- Really? I didn't know at all!
- Shalu, don't try to be funny.
- How did you turn Anand into Dev?
- No tension, Nimmi
I'll be a better Dev than Dev is!
- Yes.
- He is done for.
Respected, Ms. Sarita,
committee members...
...and my dear farmer brothers.
What I couldn't learn in America
is that...
...one must value sentiments
in one's business dealings.
What America could not teach me,
your city Palampur has taught me.
- Yeah!
- Well said.. Well said.
Isn't he talking too much?
I assure you, I will pull your city
out of the path of difficulties...
...and place it on the path of progress.
What's wrong with our people?
They're applauding every dialogue.
And this is no empty promise.
The biggest proof is that...
...instead of 800 Rupees for
every quintal of apples...
...I'll pay you 1000 Rupees
for every quintal.
Has he gone mad? He's going to
make us sink with him!
- Did you teach him all that?
- I asked him to okay 800 Rupees.
But the idiot is going berserk.
This chap is doing a somersault.
I find it all very fishy.
Find out from Roopchand and Khoobchand
what this is all about.
Okay.
There's some more good news.
What's coming now?
We're going to launch a new product.
An apple-juice...
...unrivalled by any other fruit juice
or soft drink.
And we'll call it...
..Refresh.
He couldn't have thought of all that.
You must certainly have tutored him!
Believe me, sis!
He's making it all up!
If I knew he'd do this,
I wouldn't have brought him here.
I'm going to beat him to pulp and
serve him to people in a soft drink!
- Come, sir. Come.
- Where?
Over there.
- He's a driver!
- Inspector, arrest him.
Let's go downstairs.
- He even looks like a fraud!
- He's a driver.
He's fooling everyone
by impersonating Dev.
- Shut up.
- Inspector, I'm Dev Khanna.
Dinesh Khanna's son.
- He's Dinesh Khanna's driver's son.
- Don't you lie! Mr. Mittal.
That's impossible!
My daughter would never lie.
- But she has already lied, lady!
- Try a slap. He'll squeal!
Mr. Mittal.
- Are you the driver?
- Speak only the truth.
Inspector, how do I convince you
that I'm Dev Khanna!
I am sorry.
Not me, not anyone in this hall will
believe that you are Dev Khanna.
Shalu, tell me the truth.
He's Dev, isn't he? Mr. Khanna's son?
- Or is he a driver?
- Shalu, I'm Dev!
I'm Dev, Shalu!
- Look at me and answer me, Shalu.
- So this is Dev Khanna.
- To Dev Khanna...
- ...glory be!
Here's my resignation.
Mother, I am really sorry.
- I only wanted to help you.
- Shalu please.
Don't ever try to help me again.
Mother.
Mr. Khanna? You?
How're you feeling now?
- I'm okay.
- Let me go! Leave me alone!
Dad. Dad. Dad.
- Dad. Dad. Dad.
- He is escaping. Catch him.
Dad! Am I glad you're here!
They just don't believe
that I'm your son.
Tell them the truth! Please!
Tell them the truth.
- Yes, he's my son. Dev.
- Hear that? Know who I am?
Out of my way, please.
And you wanted to be the Mayor.
He's really Dev Khanna.
What are you doing?
Now let's quietly get out of here.
So you folks now believe
that I'm Dev Khanna?
And I did not make false
promises to you.
Dad.
I'm proud of him for whatever
he has done for you today.
I assure you, that the two of us,
father and son...
...will fulfill the promises together.
Rangeela.
Mr. Khanna, meet Sameer.
He's an amazing ventriloquist.
He has just returned
from a tour of Japan.
- He has made a great name out there.
- Really? Well done.
Thank you.
- I'm glad you're here, Mama!
- Aren't you ready yet, Nimmi?
- I don't know what to wear, Mama.
- Wear this one.
- It'll look very nice on you.
- No, I've worn that several times.
Okay. In that case, wear this one.
It's brand new.
- I don't have matching ear-rings.
- So wear something...
...that has matching ear-rings.
You're being awaited downstairs.
Who, Mama? Dev?
Yes. How did you get to know?
Mama, I'll get ready and
be downstairs in 10 minutes.
10 minutes? That's too late.
He says he's in a hurry.
Maybe he's got to go somewhere.
Don't let him leave, Mama.
I'll be down there in 2 minutes.
- Two minutes means two minutes.
- Thanks.
Nimmi, I am really sorry.
This is the second time.
I mean, I'm really sorry.
What's the excuse now?
I was only looking up the house.
It's very beautiful.
Looking up the house or were you
looking for someone?
Looking for someone? Oh no.
You reacted as if I caught
you stealing something.
- What are you talking about?
- So what were you stealing?
- I mean it, I didn't...
- Tell me, quick.
How will someone, who has lost
everything, ever steal something?
You're looking great today.
Who is it?
You? How did you get in?
Simple. By pressing enter.
Will you press exit and take
the trouble of going out?
Sorry. Sorry.
If you don't like me coming here,
I'll go away.
I didn't know my driver would
be offended so quickly.
By the way, if you wish, you
can stay here for 2 minutes.
2 minutes? 2 minutes will pass
even as we discuss the weather.
Really? There are more interesting
things to talk about...
- ...apart from the weather.
- Such as?
Such as what you said to me
at the Town Hall yesterday.
I did? I can't remember anything.
I'd even pluck the stars
from the skies for you.
Remember?
I wasn't lying.
It's two minutes already
and I must leave.
You can't leave this
moment unfinished, Dev.
When did I ever want
to leave, Shalu?
These are the moments in which
I get to caress your breath...
...in which I see a wonderful person.
These moments can never pass.
- You'll always find them frozen in time.
- Enough. Say nothing more, Dev.
Whatever it is...
...this is the most beautiful
moment of my life.
And I don't want to lose it ever.
You came into my life
as a stranger...
...but you own it now.
- Sameer! You're back!
- Shalu.
- Hi, Rangeela.
- Hi.
Sameer.
"Love."
"Faith gives peace to the heart."
"Wait torments the heart."
"Love."
"Faith gives peace to the heart."
"Wait torments the heart."
"My love, tonight I see...
...love in your eyes."
"Love."
"Faith gives peace to the heart."
"Wait torments the heart."
"My love, tonight I see...
...love in your eyes."
"Love."
"Faith gives peace to the heart."
"Wait torments the heart."
"Love is an intoxicating desire,
perhaps unknown to you."
"Only those in love know,
oh, what fun it is."
"In love, we meet,
and we part too."
"Love knows the colour of faith,
and treachery too."
"Crazed lovers live for love,
and die for love."
"Love...
...is the right of the heart."
...the longing tortures the heart."
"Facts, buried in love.
And tales too."
"Someone smiles,
someone is brought to tears."
"If there's restlessness,
there's solace in love too."
"There's a victory in love,
a sense of loss too."
"Lovers love to perish
in the flame of love."
"Lovers love to perish...
...in the flame of love."
"Love...
...makes the heart pine."
...the wait is killing."
"Love...
...gives solace to the heart."
...the wait tortures the heart."
"My love, tonight I see...
...love in your eyes."
Shalu.. Shalu.
Mother.
Where's Shalu?
Haven't seen her all day.
She left for work early.
They're preparing for a product launch.
She's so dedicated.
- But you don't feel like working?
- Come on Mamma.
What mother? What time is it?
Here you are sitting and humming away
instead of going to work? What gives?
Mother.
Sometimes, I feel like being alone.
Goodness! What are you making of it?
Princess, I'm your mother.
Nine months you lived in my womb.
And you've grown to all of 22
right in front of my eyes.
Sweetheart, I even know
how your heart beats.
Then I've nothing to hide from you,
go on, ask me whatever you want.
Are you in love with Dev?
You must tell me the truth.
Don't ever lie to me.
- I don't know.
- Don't you?
Actually I love talking to him,
listening to him.
When I'm with him, I feel lost
and when he isn't around...
...all I think of is him,
weaving fantasies.
- Is that how you thought of Papa?
- Yes it happened.
Papa loved you very much?
Dev is a very nice boy.
He will make you very happy
I am so happy for you.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
Welcome to the biggest and
most unique fruit juice launch ever.
You'll be happy to know what
market research says.
Refresh can take on any brand
in this country.
I'll show you how the best quality
juices are produced in our factory.
- Nice beginning.
- Wait and watch.
I can't take my eyes off a beauty.
Your father is staring.
This drink was sampled here and abroad.
Here are the responses.
Hi, how do you find Refresh?
Excellent,
I tried it first and it is the best.
Delicious and refreshing.
How do you find Refresh?
Very fresh and very tasty.
This is the best.
- It's all fake.
- Must be actors on pay.
- What to do with them?
- Rip off and get rid.
Shut up.
For the sake of product recall,
multinationals spend millions...
...using film stars, cricketers, models.
- Correct.
- But we want to do different...
...absolutely original.
We're using a star...
...who has given our city
a new identity.
- The one and only. Sameer.
- Wow.
Our country is proud of you.
Yeah Sameer, way to go!
As if they've roped in a film star.
- Hello, everybody.
- Hello, hello.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Thank you for selecting me
as your product mascot.
Not you!
They've chosen me, moron.
So let's make Refresh
the greatest juice in the world.
Got to prove a point!
Let's get to work.
After years, I feel the same
enthusiasm I had...
...when I started this factory.
I want us to work hard...
...to make a success of this launch.
And like our mascot says...
...got to prove a point!
So let's get to work.
- Yeah!
"There's fun in the air...
...and the colour of love."
"You know what... my
heartbeat says?"
"From now, my love,
my heart is yours."
"There's fun in the air...
...and the colour of love."
"You know what... my
heartbeat says?"
"From now, my love,
my heart is yours."
"Secretly, I have loved you..."
"...it's true, sweetheart."
"How you made me pine..."
"...I can't tell you in words."
"Nobody knows... how
we fell in love."
"I love nobody... more
than I love you."
"You know... what
my heartbeat says?"
"From now, my love,
my heart is yours."
"Love is in the air."
"I'm lost."
"I'm lost in my dreams."
"I'm crazy."
"I don't think...
...I can live without you."
"You know what... my
heartbeat says?"
"From now, my love...
...my heart is yours."
"There's fun in the air...
...and the colour of love."
"You know what... my
heartbeat says?"
"From now, my love...
...my heart is yours."
- ...my heart is yours.
- "My heart is yours."
- "My heart is yours.
- My heart is yours."
- Murthy...
- Yes sir.
...table booked at the
Chinese restaurant?
Yes, sir.
- Everyone gone?
- Yes, sir.
- What a scoundrel you are!
- Sir.
What a scoundrel you are!
- Look, when the factory is mine....
- Yes.
- I'll make you my manager!
- Thanks boss.
It's important for us
that the launch fails.
Yes sir.
Suck Khanna Industries dry
at double speed.
Everything's ready for tonight.
How many trucks do we engage?
Enough to empty all the godowns.
Come on. Let's go.
Here we are.
- Hurry up and come down.
- Coming, sir.
- Come out quickly.
- Sure, sir.
Tell them to hurry up. All trucks
must be out in half an hour.
Will be done.
- Load the stuff quickly.
- This stuff...
- So many traitors?
- Now I know...
...where all the profits are going.
Khanna Industries was
never making losses.
These guys were lining their pockets.
Disgusting.
They not only cheated us,
but also the farmers and all of Palampur.
Is my son speaking the truth?
I took you for a brother,
I trusted you.
- How could you stoop so low?
- My brother is innocent.
He didn't know what's going on.
I'm the real traitor.
- Brother.
- Not a word, brother.
For the sake of our mother.
I stabbed you in the back
for my gain.
No.
It's as big a shock for you
as it is for me.
You brother has hurt me.
But now...
...my son is managing this factory.
It's going to be his decision.
Lost the gamble!
My brother has been jailed.
You've lost no gamble. Just one
thorn out of our way...
...and the factory is ours.
Look! He's coming straight at us.
Good! Lf you say so,
I'll run him over.
No! My brother is in jail!
Things could get worse.
- No better a chance! Say yes!
- No.
- Dev.
- Hey. Hi, Nimmi.
Hi.
He threw your brother in jail.
I'll send him to heaven.
No. No. Don't do it.
Dev. Dev. Watch out.
Nimmi. Nimmi.
Nimmi. Oh, God. Nimmi.
Nimmi.
- Sister.
- Hey, Shalu.
Oh my god. How did this happen?
- Are you all right?
- Minor bruises.
- Minor? What did the doctor say?
- You didn't inform Ma?
She's away on important work,
she will get worried.
- Don't telephone her.
- I didn't. Relax.
Don't worry about your sister.
I'm taking care of her.
- Am I taking good care of you?
- Yes.
Yes.
- Hi, Nimmi.
- Dev.
- Hi. Thank you.
- This is for you.
What a lucky day!
Wow!
- Seeing you after 4 days!
- And I'm seeing you...
...after 4 days, 8 hours,
31 minutes and 5 seconds.
Don't ask me how hard every second was.
In memory of me.
I hope you haven't built a Taj Mahal?
Try this out.
No Taj Mahal.
- But something beautiful. For you.
- Tell me, what?
- It's something.
- Come on, show me.
Couldn't fit in my pocket.
So I sent it home for you.
Home?
- Let it come in. Let it in.
- Shut up.
Screaming won't get it in.
Tilt it to a side.
- Careful.
- Oh, my God.
Such a huge gift?
Who's this crazy?
Open it up. Fast.
Wow!
What a beautiful gift!
Who sent it?
Dev.
Swear that you love me.
I love you Dev! I swear.
I love you.
Shalu.
Sister.
- Sister.
- Shalu, I am so happy.
Look! What a gift!
Yes, Shalu.
- Sister, is it true?
- You think it's a dream?
Yes.
"Swear when you say..."
"Smile when you say."
"Say with all your heart."
"Come into my arms when you say."
"You love me."
"Say it even if you're shy."
"Say it even if it staggers you."
"And whether you mean it or not."
"Just keep saying it."
"You love me."
"When I see you, a strange desire...
...stirs my heart."
"Whenever I see you...
...I want to love you."
"What being in love means...
...I can't tell you in words."
"Never stay out of my sight..."
"...my love."
"Say it even if you're too
proud to admit it."
"And dazzle me when you say it..."
"And whether you mean it or not."
"Just keep saying it."
"You love me."
Shalu! I'm so happy today!
And it's all because of you.
If not for you, Dev wouldn't be
in my boutique...
...I wouldn't fall into his arms
or looked into his eyes...
...I wouldn't be in love and
this gift would never be mine.
Shalu I love him dearly! But I didn't
know that he loves me too.
But he was so caring in the hospital,
he spent so much time with me...
...it was the most beautiful day
in my life. And now this gift.
I think I'm going crazy!
Shalu, come downstairs.
Come down.
Sure, sister.
Oh, Sister.
I am so happy for you.
What a joy! The two of you
love each other so dearly.
Mother.
- Mother.
- What happened?
- I'm so happy.
- I can see that.
- But what happened?
- Come with me. Just come with me.
- What's up Nimmi?
- I must show you something.
- Come on.
- I'll fall down.
- What do you want to show me?
- Look Mamma.
- What?
- Oh, my God.
Such a huge gift? From Dev?
I know he is so sweet.
He loves me and I love him, too.
- I love him. I love him.
- Yes. Yes. Yes. He loves you.
- Should I speak to Mr. Khanna?
- What's the hurry?
I can see the eagerness in your eyes.
And that's proof of how crazy he is.
I'm going to talk to Mr. Khanna
about your wedding right away.
Oh, Mother, thank you.
Shalu. Shalu.
Where have you been all day?
Dev has been looking for you.
I am so sorry.
You know, the launch deadlines.
Tell Dev, I'll see him in 5 minutes.
Make sure. Or he'll kill me.
Launch.
Murthy can we prepone the
bank appointment, please?
Okay, I'll see you in five minutes.
- Narayan where's Shalu?
- In her office.
What? In office.
- I've been looking forever!
- She's right here.
- Where is she?
- She was here. Has she vanished?
- I don't get this...
- Here she is.
Shalu. Shalu. What is this, Shalu?
All day you've been playing
hide n seek with me.
Hide-n-seek?
- You got me into this launch.
- Can't spare a minute for me?
I've got to get the designs approved
and the deadline is coming up.
- I'm too busy to eat! Spare me.
- I haven't eaten either.
- Let's go and eat in the canteen.
- No Dev.
- No Dev please.
- Come on. Come on.
It must be a Wednesday special, today.
Mr. Roopchand, later.
You're shy, as if I'm a stranger.
You didn't like my gift?
- No, it's exotic.
- Not more than you are.
Do you know when I fell for you?
When you took me to Delhi.
You spoke of the stars and the moon
and you asked me what they're about.
On that moonlit night,
you looked prettier than the Moon.
From that moment,
I've been in love with you.
I'll see you after
I've delivered these artworks.
Shalu. Shalu.
What's come over her? Have you noticed
she has been avoiding me all day.
- But why is she avoiding you?
- No idea.
And Dad wants me to
bring her home this evening.
At home? But 5 minutes ago...
...she was telling me that
she's going to the bank.
- Bank?
- Yes.
I don't know what to do?
- Idea!
- What?
I'll use the ploy of going to
the bank to take her home.
- Correct.
- Perfect.
Right. Right.
- Hey, Dev. Cake, please.
- Oh, cake.
All the best.
- Hold it. One second.
- No, dear. I don't want.
- No Dev.
- Dev we are full.
Enough. Actually...
Not meant to be used there!
He is too much.
You won't understand.
When in love, you got to do everything.
- Mad. Very, very mad.
Hi Shalu!
Murthy will see you in the bank.
I'll drop you there.
- No Dev... what happened to your tie?
- My tie?
Oh my god, the cake! How did it happen?
I'll change in two minutes at home.
- No Dev! You go home, I'll take a cab.
- No way.
Can't cab it as long as
your lifetime-driver is with you.
I'm taking you
wherever you're going.
After I returned from America,
my son put me on a liquid diet.
This is a nice excuse, Ms Sarita.
Won't you help yourself, please?
Nice excuse for you.
Help yourself.
Mr. Khanna, I'd like to discuss
something important with you.
- Yes, tell me.
- Only I don't know...
...where to begin.
We've known each other for years.
I'd appreciate it if...
Lf.. your daughter marries my son.
You want that too?
- I've been wanting to talk to you.
- Really.
You said half of it, and so did I.
Thank god.
I didn't know how to bring it up.
Dev and Nimmi love each other dearly
so who are we to stop them?
What happened? Have some water.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I am okay.
Mr. Khanna, I want to tell you
that Nimmi is a loving daughter.
I'm sure she will be as loving
as a daughter-in-law.
Indeed. Nimmi is a lovable child.
- Then it's final?
- Well...
Many thanks. May I take your leave?
- But.. Ms. Sarita...
- Yes.
I'd like to match their horoscopes
for the peace of my mind.
Of course they will match.
I'll send you Nimmi's horoscope.
- I'll be leaving now. Greetings.
- Okay.
- Hello Ms Sarita!
- Hello, how are you Mr. Roopchand?
- The same, but not too well.
- Why, what's the matter?
Ever since my brother went to jail,
it's been embarrassing and worrisome.
- You look very happy.
- Dev is going to marry Nimmi.
- What?
- Yes - Dev and Nimmi? - Yes.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
Great news! Nimmi and Mr. Dev
will be a perfect match.
But there's something..
Should I tell you or not?
What is it?
- No, I mustn't speak of it.
- Come clean.
No doubt, Nimmi and Dev
are made for each other.
- But many a slip between cup and lip.
- What do you mean?
I hate telling you this, but Shalu's
behaviour at the office is no good.
- What?
- Yes.
One mustn't be seducing
her sister's fiance.
Dev is a good human being,
but a human nonetheless.
What are you saying?
I won't lie, I'm a praying man.
Today they were inside the lift.
And they refused to let me in!
Shut themselves inside the lift.
- It has become an everyday affair.
- Shut up! This is preposterous.
You can ask anyone at the office.
Excuse me, I'm seeing the boss.
Dev and Shalu... I mean Nimmi and Dev.
God bless the pair.
Good bye.
Shalu!
- No Dev, please!
- Shalu, what's come over you?
- Dev, let me go. Some other time.
- Please, listen to me.
- No Dev, please.
- Just meet Dad. Come on.
- No Shalu.
- Please! Let me go.
No Shalu.
You must tell me, what happened?
Why have you changed overnight?
- Why have you been avoiding me?
- I'll tell you some other time.
- Shalu, have I said something wrong?
- No Dev.
- Come on Shalu.
Shalu.
Good evening, Mother.
You see Shekhar? Mother and daughter
laughing at me, they're ridiculing me.
Twenty years ago, that woman took away
all the happiness in my life.
She wrecked my home!
Now her daughter is robbing
our daughter of her joys.
But I'm not going to let that happen!
Not as long as I live! Never!
What happened Mamma? Why are you
so worried? Whom are you talking of?
- The one you love like a sister!
- Shalu?
Yes Shalu! You don't know
what she's doing behind your back.
- She's just like her mother! Wanton!
- Like her mother? I don't get you.
What are you saying? Why are you
talking like this about Shalu?
You want to know? I'll tell you
the truth about her.
Good evening, Mother.
- Hi, Sister.
- Hi.
Sitting here on a lovely evening
when romance is in the air?
You should've gone
on a dinner date with Dev.
In your place, I wouldn't leave
Dev alone for a minute.
- I would've tagged along everywhere.
- Stop that banter.
- We both know that...
- Mother, please.
Shalu, not today.
I'll call him some other day.
Something happened?
Why are you silent?
- Shalu, you know...
- Mother.
You're hiding something from me.
What's the matter, Sister?
Nothing Shalu. Nothing.
- Something happened, Mamma.
- Stop feigning.
Don't you dare call me Mamma.
- I'm not your Mamma.
- Mother please.
No Nimmi! Let her know who she is,
what's the truth about her.
She must know the foul blood
that runs in her veins.
What's come over you? Why are you
being so harsh with me, Mamma?
I told you I'm not your Mamma.
Why don't you understand that?
Your mother was the one
who poisoned my life and Nimmi's.
Mother, please.
Enough! Please calm down.
Come upstairs, Shalu. I'll explain.
Come on.
Stop Nimmi! I'm not through.
Shalu, your father married me.
Nimmi is our daughter.
And your mother, I never knew
when they began living together.
Imagine the character,
the upbringing of a woman...
...who has an illicit relationship
with a married man.
You are the illicit daughter
born of that illicit relationship.
Shalu, I'm with you.
Whatever the truth,
we're still sisters.
No Nimmi. For 20 years, I hid it.
For the sake of my promise to Shekhar.
I gave her my name, I reared her
like my daughter.
And I told the world
she is my daughter.
I never married again...
...because I didn't want our past
to ruin your happinesses.
I gave her whatever I gave you.
What I did for you, I did for her.
But the very sight of her
would never let my wound heal.
Shalu, 20 years ago, your mother
robbed me of the joys of life.
Today, will you do the same
to my daughter?
- No.
- No Shalu, I'll never let you succeed.
- Mother.
- Never.
Done Mamma?
Coughed up the venom of 20 years?
Or is there any more left?
Come Shalu.
Shalu, tell me the truth! What were
you doing with Dev in his house?
- What is your relationship with Dev?
- Don't raise this topic.
Why must I not? I will. Shut your ears
if you don't want to hear.
But this will be decided today.
- Mother please.
- Nimmi! Go to your room.
Shalu, what have I left undone for you?
Why have you done this to your sister?
The same sister who loves you,
always takes your cause...
...the sister who'd die for you!
Why did you do this Shalu?
No Mamma! I can't imagine doing it!
I love Nimmi, she is everything for me.
Lies! White lies!
Get this clear Shalu, no one's
stopping Dev from marrying Nimmi.
- You will never succeed!
- You are getting me wrong Mamma.
It'll take you some time
to get over calling me Mamma.
But whether you want it or not, I am
your mother, until Dev married Nimmi.
After that, it's you and your destiny.
"Longing and suffering in silence...
...make strange poetry."
"I try to feel..."
...every breath is painful.
"I try to understand,
yet I know little..."
...the joys and sorrows that's life.
"Sometimes it rains,
sometimes, it's autumn...
...seasons come, seasons go."
"Through smiles and tears in joy...
..in sorrow, life is lived."
"Life is all about joys and sorrows."
Shalu. Shalu. Shalu. Shalu.
Shalu, listen to me!
Whatever Mamma says...
...whatever the world says,
you and I know how close we are.
- I'm your sister, I'll always be.
- Yes sister.
One more thing.
Your Mamma and my Papa were nice.
They gave me this wonderful you.
I could never have a better sister.
You know that, don't you?
Are you in love with Dev?
Tell me the truth.
- No sister. No.
- Lf you love Dev...
...then Dev is yours,
everything I have is yours.
For a sister like you,
I'd sacrifice a hundred Dev.
- No sister, you're mistaken.
- I always wanted you to be happy.
- Say nothing more. Dev is yours.
- No sister.
Sister...
...you know, you're the
greatest sister in the world.
You're also a fool.
- How could I be in love with two guys?
- Two?
You know, ever since I was a kid...
Rangeela. Sameer?
That's why you went
to see his shows at night?
You made me spend so much money.
Then everything's fine.
I'll talk to Mamma. I promise.
And then everything will be
like always.. all of us will be happy.
Yes, Sister.
Sameer.
You dog. You scoundrel. You rascal.
You think you're smart?
What you've been up to on the sly...
- ...I know.
- What have I done?
- Whatever it is, he is to blame.
- Shut up.
And I never got to know?
Sit.
- You turn out to be sly.
- Not I.. him.
You're caught out.
Shalu has told me everything.
- Shalu told you?
- What?
- Quiet, you fool!
- Sure, you fool.
- Shalu told you what?
- That you and Shalu are in love.
- Yes or no?
- Shalu said that?
No, her ghost.
Tell me, do you love her?
Tell me.
- From the depths of my heart.
- Heart and soul.
- Ever since I was a kid.
- Every moment.
- Each and every moment.
- It's only she.
- That I think of.
- Ever since you were a kid?
- And Mamma and I haven't an inkling?
- Where is Shalu? She asked me to come.
Urgent call from the office.
She had to leave. She left a message.
Massage...!
Not massage, message.
- What message?
- She's going to see you tonight.
Is it?
Yes.
- How will I wait it out till tonight?
- There's no time! She's coming.
- Yes, clean the house, get a snack...
- First of all, a ring you fool.
Yes... let's go.
Shalu, we must resolve
your mother's misconception.
Dad couldn't refuse her
when she spoke of Nimmi.
And she thinks the wedding is final.
We must tell her the truth.
No Dev. I won't hurt Mamma or sister.
Try to understand me.
You don't know,
sister loves you dearly.
Look Shalu, Nimmi may be a nice girl.
- But I love you, not Nimmi.
- Then nothing can be done.
I'm not forcing you to marry Nimmi.
But I can't hurt Mamma or Nimmi.
And what about me?
What about my love for you?
Is it of no value? Only your mother
and Nimmi mean everything to you?
Tell me Shalu. You have no place
inside your heart for me?
Dev I can imagine
what you're going through.
Do you think I don't feel?
But there's no other way!
You don't know
what my sister means to me.
She loves you dearly.
Yet, for my sake,
she's willing to sacrifice her love.
Then why.. what dilemma is this?
Why can't we say we're in love?
No Dev! Lf Mamma gets to know
everything will be destroyed.
Our family is going to be ruined!
Please, for Mamma's sake, don't do this.
Why not Shalu?
She's your mother too.
Surely she loves you as much as Nimmi?
She will be just as happy.
What destruction are you afraid of?
She isn't my biological mother.
I'm her step daughter.
She has done much for me,
she has made many sacrifices.
She wants to see you and Nimmi married.
I can't deny her this happiness.
Please, understand my predicament.
- Sameer, Shalu is here.
- Oh no. Shalu is arrived.
Ask her to sit.
I'll be there in two minutes.
- Okay.
- Sameer hurry up.
Sit, Sameer is coming.
Shalu, will you marry me?
Shalu, I'm your childhood sweetheart.
Will you marry me?
- Hurry up, hero!
- One minute Rangeela.
Sameer, I'm in trouble.
I need your help.
Sure, I'll do anything for you.
Sameer, I made a mistake.
I told my sister that we're in love.
Sameer, are you listening?
Sameer.
- Yes, I'm listening.
- Please, don't get me wrong.
The situation was such, I had to lie.
Lie?
I am sorry, Sameer.
I shouldn't have done that. But what
could I do? My sister loves him dearly.
And I want them to get married.
Sameer, will you help me?
Will you feign you're in love with me?
Sameer, why are you silent?
Sameer, do you hear me?
Why not? Of course I'll pretend
I'm in love with you.
And even you won't be able
to make out it's an act.
One minute, hold this.
Give me your hand.
Shalu, will you marry me?
Tell me Shalu.
Shalu, I'm your childhood sweetheart.
Will you marry me?
Smile.
Oh, Sameer.
Thank you.
You are my best friend.
I know.
"My beloved."
"When I meet you, I'll tell you...
...how dearly I love you."
"My beloved."
"How will I survive those nights,
how will I survive those days."
"How will I survive
the loneliness without you?"
"A painful solitude suffuses me...
...the days and nights I think of you."
"My beloved."
But why do you want to marry Nimmi?
Why do you want to ruin your life?
And you love Shalu so dearly!
Then why this suicide?
It's my love that compels me.
I can't tell you what I've been through
after Shalu refused to marry me.
It was too painful for me to bear...
...and I knew Shalu was hurting too.
Shalu is doing this for
her mother's sake.
In her place maybe I'd do the same.
If I don't marry Nimmi,
Shalu will lose everything...
...her home, her sister, her mother.
I'd never want that.
Mr. Khanna, have the horoscopes matched?
Didn't I tell you?
May congratulations to you too.
Shall we proceed with the formalities?
Okay. Good bye.
Nimmi, tell us,
what does Dev look like?
Yes. Tell us.
He's cross-eyed.
He's bald.
And he walks with a stick.
Oh, God.
He tells me, Nimmi my love,
want to go to the cinema?
- Is he really like that?
- You'll stare wide-eyed when you see.
"There came a flying pigeon."
"She applied the henna on the hands."
Congratulations Mr. Mittal, one of
your dreams is about to come true.
All his dreams will come true
and all our dreams too.
- When did you break out of jail?
- Mr. Khanna bailed me out...
- ...for the wedding. He's magnanimous!
- Mr. Dilani from Delhi.
Yes, have you any news?
Really? Very good.
Fax me the birth certificate.
Now she is trapped.
Ms. Sarita will have to step down
from the Mayor's seat.
Else, the wedding is over.
- Does your daughter work all day?
- Her name is Shalu.
Lovely name. Come, sit with us
for a while.
Tomorrow, you will be bringing
Dev over for the engagement.
I hope the bridegroom doesn't fall
for so pretty a sister-in-law.
No, she won't be able to go.
There's much to do here.
Madam, Mr. Mittal is here.
Says it's important.
I'll be back.
Two daughters and a wedding.
- Greetings.
- What are you doing here?
I thought I'd seize the opportunity
to meet you.
I'll be back.
I wanted to know who Renu Verma is?
Who Renu Verma?
I don't know any Renu Verma.
Renu Verma was related to your husband.
Let's go upstairs and talk. Come on.
No matter how much you try to hide,
but the filthy truth outs, no?
Your husband Shekhar had an illicit
relationship with Renu Verma. Not true?
What nonsense! Get out of here!
I said get out from here.
Raise your voice to your detriment.
- Lf the guests hear, you will lose face.
- Will you leave, or won't you?
Ms. Sarita...
...Shalu is your husband's illicit child.
Is it not true?
Now no lies.
Here's Shalu's birth certificate.
It mentions her mother's name clearly.
Which is Renu Verma.
What's written in a birth certificate
makes no difference to me.
If it makes no difference,
why have you concealed it?
Why give the impression
that she is your daughter?
Who are you to ask?
I will not do what you wish.
Do not be hasty, and think it over.
Do you want this wedding called off?
Would you have your daughter suffer
for the sake of an illegitimate?
How is Nimmi to blame?
Would you rather like that Nimmi
remains a maid for life?
Whatever you say, I will not allow
this city to be ruined.
For God's sake, leave me
and my daughter alone.
How can I let you be?
I too want to become Mayor.
Here's the stepdaughter.
- Is this a confrontation?
- You think you will scare us...
...with your empty threats?
You cannot hurt us.
Shalu go away.
I do not need your help.
- Mamma please, this man...
- What's this Mamma-Mamma?
She isn't your mother. Look, here's
your original birth certificate.
No piece of paper
can change my mother.
She is my real Mamma.
That's what she stays.
Shalu, you aren't my daughter, you can
never be. And if I suffer this day...
...it's because of you! They're
threatening to stop Nimmi's wedding.
- No Mamma! Nimmi will surely marry.
- But how Ms. Shalu?
Dev might be modern. But will
Mr. Khanna wish to be related...
...to a family that is harbouring
an illegitimate child?
Ms Sarita, think for yourself.
If this wedding is called off...
- ...what standing are you left with?
- This wedding is happening.
- I'll tell Mr. Khanna everything.
- Shalu! Shalu!
Shalu! Stop! You tell him?
So that he can call off this wedding?
- No, Mother.
- Just try. Go, please go.
- Mama.
- Shalu.
Shalu, stop! Shalu! Shalu!
Stop I say.. listen to me, Shalu.
Ms. Sarita, what happened?
Any problem?
Shalu.
Shalu. Ms. Sarita, what happened?
Tell the driver to get the car.
"Beloved, we're celebrating.."
"Beloved, we're celebrating."
"Your dearest.."
"Your dearest sisters-in-law
are all dressed up."
"Are all dressed up for the occasion."
"Sit for a while.."
"Sit for a while with me."
"I love to hear you talk."
- Look please.
- Why only one? Have one more.
"Oh my Almighty, my Jugni."
"Oh my brother, my Jugni."
"Come on boys, let's dance."
"Give me another drink, my friend."
"I'll once again..."
Shalu, what happened?
Are you alright?
Say something.
What is the problem?
Oh my god!
- Excuse me sir.
- Yes.
Shalu is here. She looks worried.
Something's amiss.
She looks tense
and she's saying nothing.
Excuse me.
Uncle.
Uncle, I'd like...
...I'd like...
- Uncle I...
- Yes, my child?
Uncle I...
Speak.
Tell me, my child.
Uncle.
Uncle, what's wrong with me?
Why is everyone worried
because of me?
Why, particularly, my Mamma?
And she's...
She isn't my Mamma.
Till today, I have been
considering her as my mother.
It was a saving grace
that she lent me her name.
I love her dearly,
but she isn't my Mamma.
My parents died 20 years ago
in an accident.
You tell me,
is it my mistake to be a stepdaughter?
Is it Mamma's fault
that I am her stepdaughter?
Uncle after knowing that Nimmi
and I are step sisters...
..will you call off this wedding?
Am I so wretched...
...that you will refuse to have
any relationship with my family?
Am I so evil...
...that my Mamma and my sister
must suffer for my existence?
Uncle please.
She loves me so dearly.
Is she the child I have
despised all my life?
How is she to blame
for whatever happened?
She loves me and Nimmi so dearly?
I don't care what Mr. Khanna decides.
I just want to hold
this loving daughter to my bosom.
Bless you, child.
For a stepdaughter like you...
...I'd give up
a thousand of my offsprings.
Have no worry,
this wedding will surely happen.
But I must commend your courage.
Before so many people, you spoke
the truth about yourself?
Be happy.
I never knew my father.
But I think he must've been like you.
If you consider me to be like
a father, will you answer a question?
Honestly... have you never loved Dev?
No. Only Nimmi loves Dev.
Thank you, Uncle.
I want to give Mamma the good news
right away.
Thank you, Dev.
Thank you so much.
Wonderful...
...such a selfless sacrifice.
"Come riding a white horse like a prince."
"Marry me and take me away."
Sister.. Sister. Your mother is back.
- Where is Shalu?
- Upstairs.
Sarita, where have you been?
Give me a reply.
Mamma! I spoke to Uncle Khanna!
He won't call off the wedding.
I know, I heard everything.
Forgive me Shalu, I always
thought ill of you.
You're my daughter, aren't you?
My own, aren't you?
My baby, forgive me. My baby.
Mamma, for the first time ever
you embraced me.
Don't let go of me so soon.
My baby.
My baby! I will always hold you
in my arms, forever.
Your mother must've been a great woman
to have borne a daughter like you.
Believe me Shalu, I never knew
that you and Dev were in love.
You needn't make
such a great sacrifice.
- I'll talk to Nimmi, it'll all be fine.
- No.
She's ready for the wedding,
tomorrow's the engagement.
She will have a heartbreak.
Sister has her Dev, I have my mother
I want nothing more.
Look. Look there.
"I've given you my heart,
I am in love with you."
"I am in love with you."
"I've given you my heart,
I am in love with you."
"I am in love with you."
"I've stolen your heart,
because you said yes."
"Because you said yes."
"I've given you my heart,
I am in love with you."
"I am in love with you."
"My beloved, my sweetheart,
I dance to your tune."
"Hush, someone might hear."
"I have loved you, I didn't rob you."
"I didn't force you."
"I've made you restless,
because I make you pine."
"I've made you restless."
"I've given you my heart,
I am in love with you."
"I am in love with you."
"Never in midstream...
...leave me, never break my heart."
"How can I tell you how I suffer?"
"lf I live for you, I'll die for you."
"I have found you now,
after waiting so long for you."
"After waiting so long for you."
"I've given you my heart,
I love you."
"I am in love with you."
Sameer.
What is the matter?
Why are you so sad?
- It's nothing, Nimmi.
- Surely it's something.
- You're hiding something from me.
- You see, the truth always outs.
What truth is Rangeela speaking of?
Nimmi, whatever is happening is wrong.
Yes.
Nimmi, I didn't mean to hurt you.
No, you saved me from doing...
...what I'd never forgive myself for.
Shalu did all this for my happiness?
Does she not understand?
If she and Dev love each other...
...how can I be happy with Dev?
Not everyone is destined to find love.
But to love someone
is within everyone's grasp.
No matter if it remains a dream.
As long as the dream was, it was fine.
If it's no more, then so be it.
That's life.
Sameer, we've both been in love.
But we're still to do our duty.
You're right, not all is over.
To make this launch memorable...
...I'll share some news with you.
My son Dev is marrying
Ms. Sarita's daughter.
Come on, Sister.
What are you doing?
He's talking about you and Dev.
Shalu, how did you and Mamma imagine
that I'd be happy if you are unhappy?
Silly. Dev loves you. Only you.
- Then how can I marry him?
- No sister.
Luckily Sameer told me everything.
Or, I'd never be able to forgive myself.
You're a darling and you deserve
all the happiness in the world.
You did the right thing, Nimmi.
I am so proud of you.
"There's fun in the air...
...and the colour of love."
"You know what... my
heartbeat says?"
"From now, my love..
..my heart is yours."
"There's fun in the air...
...and the colour of love."
"You know what... my
heartbeat says?"
"From now, my love..
..my heart is yours."
"Love."
"Faith gives peace to the heart."
"Wait torments the heart."
"Love."
"Faith gives peace to the heart."
"Wait torments the heart."
"My love, tonight I see...
...love in your eyes."
"Love."
"Faith gives peace to the heart."
"Wait torments the heart."
"My love, tonight I see...
...love in your eyes."
"Love."
"Faith gives peace to the heart."
"Wait torments the heart."
♪ Hope it helped -> bozxphd ♪